<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Cloud on Marco's Tech Blog</title><link>https://blog.marcozh.com/tags/cloud/</link><description>Recent content in Cloud on Marco's Tech Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.marcozh.com/tags/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Cloud Resume Challenge, Part 2 - Hosting Static Webpage with AWS S3, CI/CD in AWS and Frontend</title><link>https://blog.marcozh.com/post/2023-03-25_cloud-resume-challenge-part2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.marcozh.com/post/2023-03-25_cloud-resume-challenge-part2/</guid><description>Frontend The frontend is pretty straight forward, I used React for writing up my resume webpage, but you can choose from any JavaScript framework of your preference. I am not going to talk too much on frontend because this is not the main focus of this challenge.
CI/CD I used AWS CodePipeline for CI/CD of this challenge. The CI/CD pipeline is triggered by code change in the nominated code repository, in my case this is on AWS CodeCommit, but you can use GitHub or other Git services.</description></item><item><title>The Cloud Resume Challenge, Part 1 - Introduction</title><link>https://blog.marcozh.com/post/2023-03-23_cloud-resume-challenge-introduction/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blog.marcozh.com/post/2023-03-23_cloud-resume-challenge-introduction/</guid><description>Introduction I recently completed The Cloud Resume Challenge and found it very interesting. I bought my first ever domain, and explored some basic AWS services. This project definitely gets me started on AWS and how powerful it is, so I encourage you to try too. In the next few blogs, I am going to write up how I completed this prject and what I have learned.
Why This Challenge I have always been very keen in Cloud related technology ever since I first heard the term from university course.</description></item></channel></rss>